DIEGO BUZANELLO

• DETAILS •

Rua dos Pica Paus, 25 São Paulo, SP - BR +55 11 964330683 buzanello.diego@gmail.com

· LINKS ·

Linkedin: /in/diego-buzanello GitHub: /diegobuzanello Behance: /buzanello_diego

• SOFTWARES •

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Adobe InDesign Adobe XD Sketch Figma

Visual Studio Code Sublime

> Windows Linux Mac

• LANGUAGES •

Portuguese English

PROFILE

Front-end developer, passionate about learning and creating clean and organized code. Also focused on accessibility and best practices.

Experienced with the JavaScript language, as well as its main frameworks and libraries, such as Angular and React.

Finishing bachelor's degree in Digital Design at Anhembi Morumbi this year (2020).

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Front-End Developer at hiBike, São Paulo

December 2019 - Present

App development (Ionic, Angular), maintain and design web pages (Wordpress), PHP (Laravel), UX/UI, creation of graphic and digital arts.

UX/UI Designer / Intern at SaveAdd, São Paulo

November 2019 - December 2019

Design and creation of institutional website and assistance in the development of an application's navigation / interface.

Web Developer / Intern at Criaturo, São Paulo

February 2019 - October 2019

Web development (HTML, CSS and JavaScript), banners, layout creation, UX/UI, Wordpress, graphic and digital arts.

■ EDUCATION

Digital Design, University Anhembi Morumbi, São Paulo

February 2017 - Present

Computer Science, UNIOESTE, Paraná

January 2016 - June 2016

Computer Science, FMU, São Paulo

August 2015 - December 2015

COURSES

Inglês, Cultura Inglesa

February 2009 - December 2013

Desenvolvimento Web 2019, Udemy

February 2019 - August 2019